Guide to the Native American subject vertical file [ca.1850-2000.]
Native American subject vertical file
- Folklore - Aleuts (Box 50)
- Folklore - Algonquian (Box 50)
- Folklore - Apache (Box 50)
- Folklore - Arapaho (Box 50)
- Folklore - Aztecs (Box 50)
- Folklore - Bibliography (Box 50)
- Folklore - Blackfoot (Box 50)
- Folklore - Caingang (Box 50)
- Folklore - Canada (Box 50)
- Folklore - Central America - See also Folklore Kekchi, Folklore - Quiches (Box 50)
- Folklore - Cherokee (Box 50)
- Folklore - Cheyenne (Box 50)
- Folklore - Chippewa 1 (Box 50)
- Folklore - Chippewa 2 (Box 50)
- Folklore - Clallam (Box 50)
- Folklore - Comanche (Box 50)
- Folklore - Cree (Box 50)
- Folklore - Cree - Articles & Corres. (Box 50)
- Folklore - Crow (Box 50)
- Folklore - Crow - Articles & Corres. (Box 50)
- Folklore - Dakota (Box 50)
- Folklore - Dakota - Articles & Corres. (Box 50)
- Folklore - Delaware (Box 50)
- Folklore - Diegueno (Box 50)
- Folklore - Eskimos (Box 50)
- Folklore - Eskimos - Articles & Corres. (Box 50)
- Folklore - Haida (Box 50)
- Folklore - Hopi (Box 50)
- Folklore - Huichol (Mexico) (Box 50)
- Folklore - Huron (Box 50)
- Folklore - Iowa Indians (Box 50)
- Folklore - Iroquois (Box 50)
- Folklore - Iroquois - Articles & Corres. (Box 50)
- Folklore - Karuk (Box 50)
- Folklore - Kekchi (Guatemala) (Box 51)
- Folklore - Kutchin (Box 51)
- Folklore - Lillooet (Box 51)
- Folklore - Makah (Box 51)
- Folklore - Makiritare (Box 51)
- Folklore - Malecite (Box 51)
- Folklore - Mataco (Box 51)
- Folklore - Menomini (Box 51)
- Folklore - Mexico (Box 51)
- Folklore - Miami (Box 51)
- Folklore - Micmac (Box 51)
- Folklore - Micmac - Articles & Corres. (Box 51)
- Folklore - Mission Indians (Box 51)
- Folklore - Mohawk (Box 51)
- Folklore - Mohegan (Box 51)
- Folklore - Mono (Box 51)
- Folklore - Montagnais (Box 51)
- Folklore - Montagnais - Naskapi (Box 51)
- Folklore - Muskhogean (Box 51)
- Folklore - Nahua (Box 51)
- Folklore - Navajo (Box 51)
- Folklore - Nez Perce (Box 51)
- Folklore - Northwest Coast (Box 51)
- Folklore - Omaha (Box 51)
- Folklore - Osage (Box 51)
- Folklore - Oto (Box 51)
- Folklore - Paiute (Box 51)
- Folklore - Papago (Box 51)
- Folklore - Passamaquoddy (Box 51)
- Folklore - Pawnee (Box 51)
- Folklore - Penobscot (Box 51)
- Folklore - Peru (Box 51)
- Folklore - Piegan (Box 51)
- Folklore - Pima (Box 51)
- Folklore - Pomo (Box 51)
- Folklore - Pueblo Indians (Box 51)
- Folklore - Quiches (Box 51)
- Folklore - Quileute (Box 51)
- Folklore - Salish 1 (Box 51)
- Folklore - Salish 2 (Box 51)
- Folklore - Sarsi (Box 51)
- Folklore - Sauk and Fox (Box 51)
- Folklore - Seminole (Box 51)
- Folklore - Shasta (Box 51)
- Folklore - Shawnee (Box 51)
- Folklore - South America (Box 51)
- Folklore - Tahltan (Box 51)
- Folklore - Tarahumara (Box 51)
- Folklore - Tepehuane (Box 51)
- Folklore - Tete de Boule (Box 51)
- Folklore - Tlingit (Box 51)
- Folklore - Tsimhian (Box 51)
- Folklore - Ute (Box 51)
- Folklore - Wichita (Box 51)
- Folklore - Winnebago (Box 51)
- Folklore - Yahgan - Tierra del Fuego (Box 51)
- Folklore - Yucatecs (Box 52)
- Folklore - Yuchi (Box 52)
- Folklore - Yuma (Box 52)
- Folklore - Zuni (Box 52)
- Folson Complex (Box 52)
- Folson Complex - Articles & Corres. (Box 52)
- Foods and Recipes 1 (Box 52)
- Foods and Recipes 2 (Box 52)
- Foods and Recipes 3 (Box 52)
- Foods and Recipes 4 (Box 52)
- Foods - Articles & Corres. 1 (Box 52)
- Foods - Articles & Corres. 2 (Box 52)
- Foods - Articles & Corres. 3 (Box 52)
- Foods - Beehive Oven (Box 52)
- Foods - Maple Sugar (Box 52)
- Foods - Potato (Box 52)
- Forestry (Box 52)
- Forts (Box 52)
- Forum (Box 52)
- Foundations (Box 52)
- Fox Indians (Box 52)
- French Guiana (Box 52)
- French Guiana - Indians (Box 52)
- Fur Trade 1 - See also: Bison; Hunting and fishing; Military and trading posts (Box 52)
- Fur Trade 2 (Box 52)
- Fur Trade - Articles & Corres. (Box 52)
- Fur Trade - Bibliography (Box 52)
- Fur Trade - Canada (Box 52)
- Fur Trade - U. S. (Box 52)
- Galleries - American Indian Community House (Box 52)
- Gambling (Box 52)
- Gambling - Articles & Corres. 1 (Box 52)
- Gambling - Articles & Corres. 2 (Box 52)
- Games (Box 52)
- Games - Articles & Corres. (Box 52)
- Games and Toys 1 (Box 52)
- Games and Toys 2 (Box 52)
- Games and Toys - Lacrosse (Box 52)
- Genealogy - Indians (Box 52)
- Georgia (Box 53)
- Georgia - Antiquities 1 (Box 53)
- Georgia - Antiquities 2 (Box 53)
- Georgia - Antiquities 3 (Box 53)
- Georgia - Antiquities 4 (Box 53)
- Georgia - Antiquities - Articles & Corres. (Box 53)
- Georgia - Indians (Box 53)
- Goajiro Indians (Colombia - Venezuela) - See also Language, Goajiro (Box 53)
- Gosiute Indians (Shoshoni) (Box 53)
- Government Relations 1 (Box 53)
- Government Relations 2 (Box 53)
- Government Relations 3 (Box 53)
- Government Relations 4 (Box 53)
- Government Relations 5 (Box 53)
- Government Relations 6 (Box 53)
- Government Relations 7 (Box 53)
- Government Relations 8 (Box 53)
- Government Relations 9 (Box 53)
- Government Relations 10 (Box 53)
- Government Relations 11 (Box 53)
- Government Relations 12 (Box 133)
  Margaret R. Elliot Collection, inventory of documents on federal government policy.
- Government Relations - Articles & Corres. 1 (Box 53)
- Government Relations - Articles & Corres. 2 (Box 53)
- Government Relations - Articles & Corres. 3 (Box 53)
- Government Relations, to 1900 (Box 54)
- Government Relations, 1940 - 1949 (Box 54)
- Government Relations, 1950 - 1969 (Box 54)
- Government Relations, 1970 - 1979 (Box 54)
- Government Relations, 1980 - 1989 (Box 54)
- Government Relations, 1990 - 1999 (Box 54)
- Government Relations, 2000 - (Box 54)
- Government Relations - Administration (Box 54)
- Government Relations - Economics (Box 54)
- Government Relations - Land (Box 54)
- Government Relations - Legal Documents 1 (Box 54)
- Government Relations - Legal Documents 2 (Box 54)
- Government Relations - Legal Documents - Articles & Corres. (Box 54)
- Government Relations - Legal Problems (Box 54)
- Government Relations - Psychological and social problems (Box 54)
- Government Relations - Religion (Box 54)
- Government Relations - Sources 1 (Box 54)
- Government Relations - Sources 2 (Box 54)
- Government Relations - Treaties (Box 54)
- Gran Chaco Indians (Box 54)
- Great Lakes Region (Box 54)
- Greenland (Box 54)
- Greenland - Antiquities 1 (Box 54)
- Greenland - Antiquities 2 (Box 54)
- Greenland - Eskimos (Box 54)
- Greenland - Eskimos - Articles & Corres. (Box 54)
- Greeting Cards (Box 54)
- Gros Ventre (Box 54)
- Guajajara Indians (Box 54)
- Gaujiro Indians (Box 54)
- Guatemala 1 (Box 54)
- Guatemala 2 (Box 54)
- Guatemala - Articles & Corres. (Box 54)
- Guatemala - Antiquities 1 (Box 54)
- Guatemala - Antiquities 2 (Box 54)
- Guatemala - Antiquities 3 (Box 55)
- Guatemala - Antiquities 4 (Box 55)
- Guatemala - Antiquities 5 (Box 55)
- Guatemala - Antiquities 6 (Box 55)
- Guatemala - Antiquities 7 (Box 55)
- Guatemala - Antiquities - Articles & Corres. (Box 55)
- Guatemala - Indians 1 (Box 55)
- Guatemala - Indians 2 (Box 55)
- Guatemala - Indians - Articles & Corres. 1 (Box 55)
- Guatemala - Indians - Articles & Corres. 2 (Box 55)
- Guato Indians (Brazil) (Box 55)
- Guayana Indians (Brazil) (Box 55)
- Haida Indians 1 - See also Folklore Haida; Language Haida (Box 55)
- Haida Indians 2 (Box 55)
- Haida. Indians - Articles & Corres. (Box 55)
- Haiti (Box 55)
- Haiti - Antiquities (Box 55)
- Haiti and Dominican Republic (Box 55)
- Haiti and Dominican Republic - Antiquities (Box 55)
- Haiti and Dominican Republic - Antiquities - Articles & Corres. (Box 55)
- Haiti and Dominican Republic - Indians (Box 55)
- Hanta Yo, ruth Beebe Hill (Box 132)
- Havasupai Indians (Yuman) (Box 55)
- Havasupai Indians - Articles & Corres. (Box 55)
- Hawaii (Box 55)
- Health and Disease 1 (Box 55)
- Health and Disease 2 (Box 133)
- Health and Disease - Articles & Corres. 1 (Box 55)
- Health and Disease - Articles & Corres. 2 (Box 55)
- Health and Disease - Aids (Box 56)
- Health and Disease - Bibliographies (Box 56)
- Health and Disease - Cancer (Box 56)
- Health and Disease - Deafness (Box 56)
- Health and Disease - Dental (Box 56)
- Health and Disease - Diabetes (Box 56)
- Health and Disease - Disabilities (Box 56)
- Health and Disease - Education (Box 56)
- Health and Disease - Handicaps (Box 56)
- Health and Disease - Indian Health Service (I.H.S) (Box 56)
- Health and Disease - Infant Care (Box 56)
- Health and Disease - Legal Documents (Box 56)
- Health and Disease - Legislation 1 (Box 56)
- Health and Disease - Legislation 2 (Box 56)
- Health and Disease - Mental Health (Box 56)
- Health and Disease - National Indian Health Board (N.I.H.B.) (Box 56)
- Health and Disease - Syphilis and Uta (Box 56)
- Health and Disease - Trachoma (Box 56)
- Health and Disease - Traditional Medicine (Box 56)
- Health and Disease - Tuberculosis (Box 56)
- Health and Disease - U. S. Dept. of Health, Education and Welfare (HEW) 1 (Box 56)
- Health and Disease - U. S. Dept. of Health, Education and Welfare (HEW) 2 (Box 56)
- Heresan Indians (Box 56)
- Hidatsa Indians (Box 56)
- Hobbyists (Box 56)
- Homosexuality, etc. (Box 56)
- Honduras (Box 56)
- Honduras - Articles & Corres. (Box 56)
- Honduras - Antiquities 1 (Box 57)
- Honduras - Antiquities 2 (Box 57)
- Honduras - Antiquities - Articles & Corres. (Box 57)
- Honduras - Antiquities (Copan) (Box 57)
- Honduras - Antiquities (Copan) - Articles & Corres. (Box 57)
- Honduras - Indians - See also Paya Indians; Xicaque Indians (Box 57)
- Hoopa & Yurok Indians - Legislation (Box 57)
- Hoopa Indians - Legislation (Box 57)
- Hopewell - See also Ohio - antiquities (Box 57)
- Hopi Indians 1 (Box 57)
- Hopi Indians 2 (Box 57)
- Hopi Indians 3 (Box 57)
- Hopi Indians 4 (Box 57)
- Hopi Indians - Articles & Corres. 1 (Box 57)
- Hopi Indians - Articles & Corres. 2 (Box 57)
- Hopi Indians - Articles & Corres. 3 (Box 57)
- Hopi Indians - Arts and Crafts - See also Folklore - Hopi; Language - Hopi; Pueblo Indians; Missions - Hopi (Box 57)
- Hopi Indians - Basket Making (Box 57)
- Hopi Indians - Ceremonies and Dances 1 (Box 57)
- Hopi Indians - Ceremonies and Dances 2 (Box 57)
- Hopi Indians - Ceremonies and Dances 3 (Box 57)
- Hopi Indians - Ceremonies and Dances - Articles & Corres. (Box 57)
- Hopi Indians - Clans and kinship (Box 57)
- Hopi Indians - Ethnobotany (Box 57)
- Hopi Indians - Hano (Box 57)
- Hopi Indians - Kachinas 1 (Box 57)
- Hopi Indians - Kachinas 2 (Box 57)
- Hopi Indians - Kachinas - Articles & Corres. (Box 57)
- Hopi Indians - Legal documents (Box 57)
- Hopi Indians - Religion 1 (Box 57)
- Hopi Indians - Religion 2 (Box 57)
- Hopi Indians - Religion - Articles & Corres. (Box 57)
- Hopi Indians - Relocation (Box 133)
- Housing 1 (Box 58)
- Housing 2 (Box 133)
  Indian Housing Authorities
- Housing and Social Programs (Box 133)
- Housing - Articles & Corres. (Box 58)
- Housing Legal Documents (Box 58)
- Huastec Indians (Mexico) - See also Language - Huastec (Box 58)
- Huave Indians (Mexico) (Box 58)
- Huichol Indians (Piman - Mexico) 1 - See also Folklore - Huichol; Language - Huichol (Box 58)
- Huichol Indians (Piman - Mexico) 2 (Box 58)
- Humor (Box 58)
- Hunting and Fishing 1 (Box 58)
- Hunting and Fishing 2 (Box 58)
- Hunting and Fishing - Articles & Corres. (Box 58)
- Huntington Free Library (Box 58)
- Hupa Indians (Athapascan) - See also Language - Hupa (Box 58)
- Huron Indians (Iroquois) - See also Folklore - Huron; Missions - Huron; Language - Huron (Box 58)
- Huron Indians (Iroquois) - Articles & Corres. (Box 58)
- Idaho (Box 58)
- Idaho - Antiquities (Box 58)
- Idaho - History (Box 58)
- Idaho - Indians (Box 58)
- Identity (Box 58)
- Illinois (Box 58)
- Illinois - Antiquities 1 (Box 58)
- Illinois - Antiquities 2 (Box 58)
- Illinois - Antiquities 3 (Box 58)
- Illinois - Antiquities - Articles & Corres. (Box 58)
- Illinois - Hstory (Box 58)
- Illinois - Indians (Box 58)
- Illinois - Indians - Articles & Corres. (Box 58)
- Implements and weapons 1 (Box 58)
- Implements and weapons 2 (Box 58)
- Implements and weapons 3 (Box 58)
- Implements and weapons 4 (Box 58)
- Implements and weapons 5 (Box 58)
- Implements and weapons 6 (Box 58)
- Implements and weapons 7 (Box 59)
- Implements and weapons 8 (Box 59)
- Implements and weapons 9 (Box 59)
- Implements and weapons - Articles & Corres. (Box 59)
- Implements and weapons - Atlatl (Box 59)
- Implements and weapons - Bannerstones (Box 59)
- Implements and weapons - Blowguns (Box 59)
- Implements and weapons - Bows and arrows (Box 59)
- Implements and weapons - Harpoons and darts (Box 59)
- Implements and weapons - Obsidian (Box 59)
- Implements and weapons - Shields (Box 59)
- Implements and weapons - Tomahawks (Box 59)
- Incas 1 - See also Kechua Indians (Box 59)
- Incas 2 (Box 59)
- Incas 3 (Box 59)
- Incas 4 (Box 59)
- Incas - Articles & Corres. (Box 59)
- Incas - Calendars (Box 59)
- Incas - Religion (Box 59)
- Indian - Arts and Crafts Board (Box 59)
- Indian - Arts and Crafts Board - Oversize (Box 130)
  Includes general information about population, also a page on Indian intellectual capacity, character, and morals.
- Indian - Black Relations (Box 59)
- Indian - Characteristics (Box 59)
- Indian Claims Commission (Box 59)
- Indian Hall of Fame (Box 59)
- Indian Health Services (Box 59)
- Indian Owned Consulting Firms (Box 132)
- Indian Reorganization Act - IRA - See also Government Relations (Box 59)
- Indian Resources Development Act - 1967 (Box 59)
- Indian Self Determination Act (Box 59)
- Indian Studies Program (Box 59)
- Indian Tribes of the United States, Canada, and Northern Mexico (Box 133)
- Indian - White Relations (Box 59)
- Indiana (Box 59)
- Indiana - Antiquities (Box 59)
- Indiana - Antiquities - Articles & Corres. (Box 59)
- Indiana - History (Box 59)
- Indiana - Indians (Box 59)
- Indigenous Peoples (Box 59)
- Inuit (Box 59)
- Iowa (Box 59)
- Iowa - Antiquities 1 (Box 59)
- Iowa - Antiquities 2 (Box 59)
- Iowa - Antiquities - Articles & Corres. (Box 60)
- Iowa - History (Box 60)
- Iowa - Indians (Box 60)
- Iowa - Indians - Articles & Corres. (Box 60)
- Iroquois (Box 60)
- Iroquois (Box 132)
- Iroquois - Antiquities (Box 60)
- Iroquois - Art (Box 60)
- Iroquois - Bibliography (Box 60)
- Iroquois - Canada (Box 60)
- Iroquois - Clothing (Box 60)
- Iroquois - Conferences (Box 60)
- Iroquois - False Faces (Box 60)
- Iroquois - Food (Box 60)
- Iroquois - Ganienkeh (Box 60)
- Iroquois - Government relations (Box 60)
- Iroquois - History 1 (Box 60)
- Iroquois - History 2 (Box 60)
- Iroquois - History 3 (Box 60)
- Iroquois - History 4 (Box 60)
- Iroquois - Implements and weapons (Box 60)
- Iroquois - League 1 (Box 60)
- Iroquois - League 2 (Box 60)
- Iroquois - League - Articles & Corres. (Box 60)
- Iroquois - Legal documents (Box 60)
- Iroquois - Individual Manuscripts (Box 60)
- Iroquois - Medicine (Box 60)
- Iroquois - Metals and metalwork (Box 60)
- Iroquois - Rites and ceremonies (Box 60)
- Iroquois - Social life and customs (Box 60)
- Iroquois - Social life and customs - Articles & Corres (Box 60)
- Iroquois - Tribal government (Box 60)
- Isleta (Box 60)
- Jacalteca Indians (Guatemala) (Box 60)
- Jade (Box 60)
- Jamaica (Box 60)
- Jamaica - Antiquities (Box 60)
- James Bay Project (Box 60)
- Jewelry (Box 60)
- Jewelry - Articles & Corres. (Box 60)
- Jewelry - Silverwork (Box 61)
- Jewelry - Southwest (Box 61)
- Jicarilla. Indians (Box 61)
- Jivaro, Indians (Box 61)
- Jivaro Indians - Articles & Corres. (Box 61)
- Journalism (Box 61)
- Juaneno Indians (Box 61)
- Jumano Indians (Box 61)
- Jurisdiction (Box 61)
- Kachinas (Box 61)
- Kansas - Antiquities (Box 61)
- Kansas - Indians (Box 61)
- Karaja Indians (Box 61)
- Karok Indians (Box 61)
- Kaw Indians (Box 61)
- Kayapo Indians (Box 61)
- Kechua Indians (Box 61)
- Kekchi Indians (Guatemala) - See also Folklore - Kekchi; Language - Kekchi (Box 61)
- Kentucky (Box 61)
- Kentucky - Antiquities 1 (Box 61)
- Kentucky - Antiquities 2 (Box 61)
- Kentucky - Antiquities - Articles & Corres. (Box 61)
- Kickapoo Indians (Box 61)
- Kickapoo Indians - Articles & Corres. (Box 61)
- Kinship (Box 61)
- Kiowa Indians (Box 61)
- Klamath Indians (Box 61)
- Klamath Indians - Legislation (Box 61)
- Klikitat Indians (Shahaptian) (Box 61)
- Knots and Knotting - See also Weaving and Textiles (Box 61)
- Koggaba Indians (Colombia) - See also Language - Koggaba (Box 61)
- Kootenai Indians (Box 61)
- Kutchin Indians (Athapascan) - See also Folklore - Kutchin (Box 61)
- Kutenai Indians (Box 61)
- Kwakiutl Indians (Wakashan) (Box 61)
- Labrador - Antiquities (Box 61)
- Labrador - Eskimos (Box 61)
- Lacandon Indians (Central America) 1 (Box 61)
- Lacandon Indians (Central America) 2 (Box 61)
- Land claims (Box 61)
- Land claims - Articles & Corres. (Box 61)
- Land claims - Legal documents (Box 61)
- Land grants (Box 61)
- Land tenure (Box 61)
- Land transfers (Box 62)
- Languages - See also: Folklore; Pictographs; Quipus; Sign language (Box 62)
- Languages - Articles & Corres. 1 (Box 62)
- Languages - Articles & Corres. 2 (Box 62)
- Language - Abnaki (Box 62)
- Language - Accawai (British Guiana) (Box 62)
- Language - Achomawi (Box 62)
- Language - Aguateco (Box 62)
- Language - Alacalufan (Tierra del Fuego) - See also: Language, Ona; Language, Yahgan (Box 62)
- Language - Alaguilac (Mayan) (Box 62)
- Language - Alaska (Box 62)
- Language - Aleut (Box 62)
- Language - Algonquian 1 (Box 62)
- Language - Algonquian 2 (Box 62)
- Language - Allentiac (Argentina) (Box 62)
- Language - Amuesha (Peru, Ecuador) (Box 62)
- Language - Andagui (Colombia) (Box 62)
- Language - Apache (Box 62)
- Language - Apolista (Bolivia) (Box 62)
- Language - Arapaho (Box 62)
- Language - Araucanian (Chile) (Box 62)
- Language - Arawakan (Box 62)
- Language - Arikara (Box 62)
- Language - Assiniboine (Box 62)
- Language - Athapaskan - See also: Language: Chastacosta; Chilula; Hupa; Navaho; Sarsi; Tinne (Box 62)
- Language - Aymara (Bolivia) (Box 62)
- Language - Beothuk (Box 62)
- Language - Bibliography (Box 62)
- Language - Bibliography - Articles & Corres. (Box 62)
- Language - Biloxi (Box 62)
- Language - Blackfoot (Box 62)
- Language - Bororo (Box 62)
- Language - Boruca (Box 62)
- Language - Caddoan - See also: Language: Arikara, Pawnee (Box 62)
- Language - Cahuapana (Box 62)
- Language - Cakchiquel (Box 62)
- Language - California 1 (Box 62)
- Language - California 2 (Box 62)
- Language - Campa (Peru) (Box 62)
- Language - Canada (Box 62)
- Language - Canari (Ecuador) (Box 62)
- Language - Canichana (Bolivia) (Box 62)
- Language - Caraja (Brazil) (Box 62)
- Language - Carib (Box 62)
- Language - Catawba (Box 62)
- Language - Cayapa (Box 62)
- Language - Cayapo (Box 62)
- Language - Cayuvava (Box 62)
- Language - Central America (Box 62)
- Language - Central America - Articles & Corres. (Box 62)
- Language - Chanabal (Box 62)
- Language - Chapacuran (Box 62)
- Language - Chastacosta (Box 62)
- Language - Cherokee (Box 62)
- Language - Cherokee - Articles & Corres. (Box 63)
- Language - Cheyenne (Box 63)
- Language - Chibchan (Box 63)
- Language - Chinantec (Mexico) (Box 63)
- Language - Chinookan (Box 63)
- Language - Chinookan - Articles & Corres. (Box 63)
- Language - Chipaya (Box 63)
- Language - Chippewa (Box 63)
- Language - Chocoan (Colombia) (Box 63)
- Language - Choctaw (Box 63)
- Language - Cholona (Peru, Ecuador) (Box 63)
- Language - Chuj (Box 63)
- Language - Classification and Studies (Box 63)
- Language - Classification and Studies - Articles & Corres. (Box 63)
- Language - Cocopa (Box 63)
- Language - Cora (Mexico) (Box 63)
- Language - Costanoan (Box 63)
- Language - Cree 1 (Box 63)
- Language - Cree 2 (Box 63)
- Language - Cree 3 (Box 63)
- Language - Cree 4 (Box 63)
- Language - Cree - Articles & Corres. (Box 63)
- Language - Creek (Box 63)
- Language - Crow 1 (Box 63)
- Language - Crow 2 (Box 63)
- Language - Cuna (Panama) (Box 63)
- Language - Dakota (Box 63)
- Language - Dakota - Articles & Corres. (Box 63)
- Language - Delaware (Box 63)
- Language - Dieguno (Box 63)
- Language - Ecuador (Box 63)
- Language - Eskimos 1 (Box 63)
- Language - Eskimos 2 (Box 63)
- Language - Eskimos - Articles & Corres. (Box 63)
- Language - Flathead (Box 63)
- Language - Fulnio (Eastern Brazil) (Box 63)
- Language - Goajiro (Colombia, Venezuela) (Box 63)
- Language - Gosiute (Box 63)
- Language - Grammatical Process (Box 63)
- Language - Gros Ventre (Box 63)
- Language - Guenoa (Uruguay) (Box 63)
- Language - Guetare (Costa Rica) (Box 64)
- Language - Haida (Box 64)
- Language - Halkomelem (Box 64)
- Language - Hopi (Box 64)
- Language - Huastec (Mayan) (Box 64)
- Language - Huichol (Mexico) (Box 64)
- Language - Huron (Iroquois) (Box 64)
- Language - Ica (Colombia) (Box 64)
- Language - Illinois (Box 64)
- Language - Ipurina (Brazil) (Box 64)
- Language - Iroquoian (Box 64)
- Language - Iroquoian - Articles & Corres. (Box 64)
- Language - Itonama (Bolivia) (Box 64)
- Language - Jacalteco (Box 64)
- Language - Jivaro (Box 64)
- Language - Kanjobal (Box 64)
- Language - Karankawa (Box 64)
- Language - Kawaiisu (Box 64)
- Language - Kechua (Box 64)
- Language - Kechua - Articles & Corres. (Box 64)
- Language - Kekchi (Mayan) (Box 64)
- Language - Keres (Box 64)
- Language - Kiowa (Box 64)
- Language - Koggaba (Colombia) (Box 64)
- Language - Kutenai (Box 64)
- Language - Kwakiutl (Box 64)
- Language - Latin America (Box 64)
- Language - Leco (Bolivia) (Box 64)
- Language - Luiseno (Box 64)
- Language - Mahican (Box 64)
- Language - Maidu (Box 64)
- Language - Makuan (Box 64)
- Language - Malecite (Box 64)
- Language - Mam (Mayan) (Box 64)
- Language - Mangue (Nicaragua) (Box 64)
- Language - Massachusetts (Box 64)
- Language - Mataco (Gran Chaco) (Box 64)
- Language - Matlatzinca (Mexico) (Box 64)
- Language - Mayan (Box 64)
- Language - Menominee (Box 64)
- Language - Mexico (Box 64)
- Language - Mexico - Articles & Corres. (Box 64)
- Language - Miami (Box 64)
- Language - Micmac (Algonquian) (Box 64)
- Language - Millcayac (Argentina) (Box 64)
- Language - Miwok (Box 64)
- Language - Mixe (Mexico) (Box 64)
- Language - Mixtec (Mexico) (Box 64)
- Language - Mobima (Bolivia) (Box 64)
- Language - Modoc (Box 64)
- Language - Moguex (Colombia) (Box 64)
- Language - Mohawk 1 (Box 64)
- Language - Mohawk 2 (Box 64)
- Language - Mohegan (Box 65)
- Language - Moki (Box 65)
- Language - Montagnais (Box 65)
- Language - Montauk (Algonquian) (Box 65)
- Language - Mopan (Box 65)
- Language - Mosquito (Central America) (Box 65)
- Language - Muskhogean (Box 65)
- Language - Nahuatl 1 (Box 65)
- Language - Nahuatl 2 (Box 65)
- Language - Nahuatl 3 (Box 65)
- Language - Nahuatl - Articles & Corres. (Box 65)
- Language - Nanticoke (Box 65)
- Language - Narragansett (Box 65)
- Language - Natchez (Box 65)
- Language - Navajo 1 (Box 65)
- Language - Navajo 2 (Box 65)
- Language - Navajo - Articles & Corres. (Box 65)
- Language - Nevada (Box 65)
- Language - New Mexico (Box 65)
- Language - Nez Perce (Box 65)
- Language - Niska (Box 65)
- Language - Nootka (Box 65)
- Language - Omaha (Box 65)
- Language - Ona (Tierra del Fuego) (Box 65)
- Language - Onondaga (Box 65)
- Language - Opata (Mexico) (Box 65)
- Language - Orthography & Spelling (Box 65)
- Language - Oregon (Box 65)
- Language - Osage (Box 65)
- Language - Oto (Box 65)
- Language - Otomi (Mexico) (Box 65)
- Language - Ottawa (Box 65)
- Language - Otuque (Eastem Bolivia) (Box 65)
- Language - Paiute (Box 65)
- Language - Pame (Mexico) (Box 65)
- Language - Panoan (Peru, Bolivia, Brazil) (Box 65)
- Language - Papabuco (Oaxaca, Mexico) (Box 65)
- Language - Papago (Box 65)
- Language - Passamaquoddy (Box 65)
- Language - Pawnee (Box 65)
- Language - Payagua (Gran Chaco) (Box 65)
- Language - Peban (Brazil) (Box 65)
- Language - Pehuenche (Argentina) (Box 65)
- Language - Penobscot (Box 65)
- Language - Peru (Box 65)
- Language - Piegan (Box 65)
- Language - Pima (Box 65)